Guide to the John Sylvester Fischer Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1928-1978, undated; Series I; 10.5 linear feet (25 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE is arranged alphabetically. Large groups of letters from a single individual or organization have been foldered separately, as has the correspondence of particularly notable people such as John F. Kennedy and John K. Galbraith. An asterisk next to the folder title indicates that that folder contains ten or more items.
  Material relating to the various branches of the Harper organization has required special treatment because it encompasses not only Fischer's own correspondence with Harper employees and with other people on behalf of Harper's, but also correspondence of Harper employees with many of the same people who corresponded with Fischer. Often one writer would exchange letters with several editors in the process of producing an article for Harper's. In order to avoid splitting up a sequence of letters in such a case, the correspondence of Fischer and other Harper employees has been filed under the name of the third party. Employees' correspondence with Fischer has been filed under the name of the Harper employee, and correspondence between Harper employees, along with anonymous memoranda and other in-house material, is filed under the appropriate Harper branch (Harper and Brothers, Harper and Row, Harper-Atlantic Sales, or Harper's Magazine). Cross-references have been provided from these Harper folders to the Harper employees.
  Folders with asterisks (*) contain ten or more items.
  - Aa-Ac (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acorn Club (*), 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ad (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Mark (*), 1947-1951, undated (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
  - Ah-Alc (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albert, Carl (*), 1962, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ald-Alla (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alle-Alv (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allen, Frederick Lewis (*), 1944-1953 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
  - Allen, Terry (Mrs. Donald) (*), 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American A (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American B-C (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American F-I (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American L-M (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American P-Americans (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - American Society of Planning Officials (*), 1964-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - And (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Andrews, Wayne (*), 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Ang-Ap (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission (*), 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Arc-Arnd (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Arno-Art (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Asb-Asc (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ash-Ass (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ashmore, Henry S., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (*), 1961-1963, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Associated Press (*), 1931-1937 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Asw-At (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Au-Az (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Baa-Bab (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bac (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bai (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bak (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bal-Bark (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Balk, Alfred (*), 1967-1974, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Barbour, Floyd B., 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Barn (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Barnes, Eleanor (Mrs. Donald)
    General note
    See: box 18, folder 619
  - Baro-Barr (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bart-Barz (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bat-Bay (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Bea-Bed (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Bee-Bei (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Beecroft, Eric (*), 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Bel (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Beloit College (Box 2, Folder 48)
    See: box 3, folder 84
  - Beng (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Benj-Bent (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Ber-Bev (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Bermel, Joyce, 1964, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Bessie, Simon Michael (*), 1949, 1965-1978 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Bh-Bj (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Binns, James H., Jr. (*), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Blac-Blak (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Blair, William McC., Jr., 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Blair, William S. (*), 1959-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 58-61)
  - Blan-Blu (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Boa-Bod (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Boe-Bol (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Bon (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Boo (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Bor-Bou (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Bov-Boy (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Bowles, Chester (*), 1952-1969 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Brad-Bram (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Bran (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Brandt, Joseph A. (*), 1932-1952, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Brau-Brei (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Bren-Bris (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Brengel, Ruth, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Brit (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Broa-Broo (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Brookings Institution (*), 1967-1978 (Box 3, Folder 78-81)
  - Brooks, Daniel (*), 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Brooks, Paul (*), 1959, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Brou-Brown (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Browne-Bry (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bub-Buc (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Bucknell University (*), 1953-1954, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Bui-Burg (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bundy, McGeorge
    See: box 8, folder 252
  - Burn-Burr (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bus-But (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Buz-By (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - 'B' unidentified (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Cae-Cali (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - California, University of, Santa Cruz (*), 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 94-96)
    See also: box 3, folder 97
  - Calkins, Robert D. (*), 1967-1969, 1974, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    See also: box 28, folder 9-10
  - Call-Calv (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Cam-Cana (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Canf-Carri (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Canfield, Cass, Sr. (*), 1943-1968 March (Box 3, Folder 101-04)
  - Canfield, Cass, Sr. (*), 1968 April-1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 105-10)
  - Canfield, Cass, Jr. (*), 1953-1973 (Box 4, Folder 111-112)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York (*), 1963-1977, undated (Box 4, Folder 113-114)
  - Carr, John Dickson (*), 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Carro-Cart (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Carv-Cass (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Cary, Joyce (*), 1949-1956, undated (Box 4, Folder 118-121)
  - Casady, Simon (*), 1936, 1961-1971 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Case, Everett N. (*), 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 123-124)
  - Cast-Caw (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Ce-Chad (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Century Association (*), 1967-1976 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Chaf-Cham (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Chan-Chic (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Chauncey, Henry, Jr.
    See: box 25, folder 882-883
  - Chicago, University of (*), 1963-1975 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Chid-Cho (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Chr-Chu (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Ci-Clai (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Clar (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Clark College (*), 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    See also: box 10, folder 303
  - Clax-Clo (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Cleveland, Harlan (*), 1951-1978 (Box 5, Folder 137-139)
  - Coa-Coffe (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Cochran, Clay L. (*), 1935-1976 (Box 5, Folder 141-149)
  - Coffee House (*), 1951-1970 (Box 5, Folder 150-151)
  - Coffi-Cofr (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Coh (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Colb-Cole (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Coll (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Colm-Colv (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Columbia University (*), 1953-1954, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    See also: box 14, folder 476
  - Com (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Conf-Connec (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Connel-Conner (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Cons-Conv (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Coo-Coq (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Cord-Corn (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Coro-Cou (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Corry, Andrew V., 1944-1951, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. (*), 1954, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Cov-Coz (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Cowles, John, Sr., 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Cowles, John, Jr. (*), 1958-1978 (Box 6, Folder 169-174)
  - Cox, Nona, 1952-1971 (*) undated (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Cra (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Cre-Crim (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Crip (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Cripps, John (*), 1934-1935, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    See also: box 26, folder 20
  - Cris-Cs (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Cu (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - 'C' unidentified (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Daf-Dale (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Daly (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Dam-Darc (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Dard-Das (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Dav-Daw (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Davis, Ellen (*), 1956, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Dea-Deg (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Dei-Dema (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Demb-Dep (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Der-Dex (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - DeVoto, Avis (Mrs. Bernard) (*), 1949-1978 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - DeVoto, Bernard, 1946-1974 (Box 6, Folder 195-198)
  - Di (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Dob-Donah (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Donal-Donn (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Dono-Doo (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Dorn, Edwin, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Dor-Doub (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Doug-Doy (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Dr (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Drucker, Peter F. (*), 1942-1976,1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 207-211)
  - Dub-Dun (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Dugger, Ronnie (*), 1969-1974 (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Dur-Dy (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - 'D' unidentified (Box 7, Folder 215)
  - Ea-Eb (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - Ec-Ei (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Ela-Ellio (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - Elliott, George P. (*), 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Ellis-Ells (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - Ellis, James R. (*), 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Em-Enc (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Eng-Env (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Ep (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Eq-Er (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Es-Eu (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Ev-Ewa (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Evans, Eli
    See: box 4, folder 113-114
  - Ewi-Ey (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Ewing (Cortez A.M.) Foundation (*), 1964-1971 (Box 7, Folder 229-230)
  - 'E' unidentified (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Fa (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Fath, Creekmore, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Fea-Ferg (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Ferr-Fet (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Fie-Finl (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Finn-Fir (Box 8, Folder 237)
  - Fisc-Fisher, E. (Box 8, Folder 238)
  - Fisher, F.-Fit (Box 8, Folder 239)
  - Fla-Flem (Box 8, Folder 240)
  - Fleming, John R. (*), 1944, 1962-1978 (Box 8, Folder 241-246)
  - Flet-Fol (Box 8, Folder 247)
  - Fon-Ford (Box 8, Folder 248)
  - Forbes, Henry S. (*), 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 249)
  - Forbes (J.M.)&Co. (*), 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 250-251)
    See also: box 16, folder 533-534
  - Ford Foundation (*), 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 252)
  - Fore-Fors (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - Fos (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - Foster, Malcolm, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 255-256)
  - Fou-Fox (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Frad-Franke (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Frankl-Fraz (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Free (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Fren-Friede (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Friedm (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Friedr-Frier (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Frit-Fry (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Ful (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Fun-Fut (Box 9, Folder 266)
  - 'F' unidentified (Box 9, Folder 267)
  - Gai-Gall (Box 9, Folder 268)
  - Gaines, Judy (*), 1969-1978 (Box 9, Folder 269-273)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth (*), 1954, 1963-1971 (Box 9, Folder 274)
  - Galp-Garr (Box 9, Folder 275)
  - Gardner, John W., 1965-1977 (Box 9, Folder 276)
  - Gars-Garv (Box 9, Folder 277)
  - Gav-Gay (Box 9, Folder 278)
  - Gavin, James M. (*), 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 279-280)
  - Ge-Gib (Box 9, Folder 281)
  - Gif-Gil (Box 9, Folder 282)
  - Gin-Gl (Box 9, Folder 283)
  - God-Goldb (Box 9, Folder 284)
  - Golde-Golds (Box 9, Folder 285)
  - Goldw-Goll (Box 9, Folder 286)
  - Golu-Gorm (Box 9, Folder 287)
  - Gordon, Caroline
    See: box 22, folder 762
  - Gorn-Gou (Box 9, Folder 288)
  - Grad-Gran (Box 9, Folder 289)
  - Gray (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - Grays-Greenb (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Greene-Gri (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Grinyer, Margaret (*), 1957-1977 (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Gro-Gru (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Gu (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1958, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - 'G' unidentified (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - Haa-Hale (Box 10, Folder 298)
  - Hagen, Beulah W. (*), 1945-1948, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 299)
  - Hall (Box 10, Folder 300)
  - Hame-Hamm (Box 10, Folder 301)
  - Hamilton, Hamish (*), 1946-1975, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 302)
  - Hamma-Hamp (Box 10, Folder 303)
  - Han-Hap (Box 10, Folder 304)
  - Harb-Harr (Box 10, Folder 305)
  - Harper & Brothers Publishers (*), 1941-1962 (Box 10, Folder 306-307)
    See also: box 1, folder 11-13 See also: box 1, folder 32 See also: box 2, folder 53 See also: box 2, folder 58-61 See also: box 3, folder 101-104 See also: box 10, folder 299 See also: box 10, folder 327-328 See also: box 10, folder 330 See also: box 13, folder 432
  - Harper & Row, Publishers, Inc. (*), 1962-1975 (Box 10, Folder 308-309)
    See also: box 1, folder 26; See also: box 1, folder 32; See also: box 2, folder 64; See also: box 3, folder 70; See also: box 3, folder 75; See also: box 3, folder 91; See also: box 3, folder 101-104; See also: box 4, folder 111-112; See also: box 7, folder 217; See also: box 8, folder 265; See also: box 9, folder 289; See also: box 10, folder 316; See also: box 10, folder 327-328; See also: box 10, folder 330; See also: box 11, folder 340; See also: box 12, folder 386; See also: box 12, folder 408; See also: box 13, folder 416; See also: box 14, folder 456; See also: box 14, folder 457; See also: box 14, folder 468-470; See also: box 20, folder 679; See also: box 21, folder 713; See also: box 24, folder 820; See also: box 24, folder 859; See also: box 25, folder 879
  - Harper-Atlantic Sales, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 310)
    See also: box 1, folder 26 See also: box 2, folder 51 See also: box 2, folder 58-61 See also: box 3, folder 82 See also: box 6, folder 180 See also: box 6, folder 188 See also: box 12, folder 372
  - Harper's Magazine (*), 1944-1978, undated (Box 10, Folder 311-315)
    See also: box 1, folder 7 See also: box 1, folder 11-13 See also: box 1, folder 23 See also: box 1, folder 37 See also: box 1, folder 39 See also: box 1, folder 41 See also: box 2, folder 51 See also: box 3, folder 82 See also: box 3, folder 89 See also: box 4, folder 117 See also: box 5, folder 156 See also: box 6, folder 184 See also: box 6, folder 190 See also: box 6, folder 191 See also: box 8, folder 261 See also: box 9, folder 286 See also: box 10, folder 300 See also: box 10, folder 330 See also: box 11, folder 338 See also: box 11, folder 353 See also: box 12, folder 372 See also: box 12, folder 408 See also: box 13, folder 412 See also: box 13, folder 413 See also: box 14, folder 453-454 See also: box 14, folder 484 See also: box 15, folder 502 See also: box 15, folder 509 See also: box 17, folder 562 See also: box 19, folder 645 See also: box 20, folder 679 See also: box 20, folder 700 See also: box 21, folder 705 See also: box 22, folder 768-770 See also: box 24, folder 845
  - Harris (Box 10, Folder 316)
  - Harris, Michaelyn (Mrs. Hugh) (*), 1955, 1965-1977 (Box 10, Folder 317)
  - Harriso-Hart (Box 10, Folder 318)
  - Harrison, Walter M. (*), 1933-1936 (Box 10, Folder 319)
  - Harv (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Harvard University Graduate School of Education (*), 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 321-322)
  - Harvard University Press (*), 1948, 1965-1971 (Box 10, Folder 323-324)
  - Harvard University Russian Research Center, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Harwood, Edwin (*), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 326)
  - Harwood, Raymond C. (*), 1946-1975 (Box 10, Folder 327-328)
  - Has-Hau (Box 10, Folder 329)
  - Haw-Hay (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Hea-Hei (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Hel-Hen (Box 10, Folder 332)
  - Heri-Hern (Box 10, Folder 333)
  - Herr-Hew (Box 10, Folder 334)
  - Hic-Hil (Box 10, Folder 335)
  - Hine, Thomas (*), 1970-1978 (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - Hir-Hiy (Box 11, Folder 337)
  - Hoa-Hog (Box 11, Folder 338)
  - Hoh-Hol (Box 11, Folder 339)
  - Hoo-Hop (Box 11, Folder 340)
  - Hor (Box 11, Folder 341)
  - Hot-Houl (Box 11, Folder 342)
  - Hous-Hoy (Box 11, Folder 343)
  - Hs-Hue (Box 11, Folder 344)
  - Huf-Hul (Box 11, Folder 345)
  - Hughes, Jack (*), 1947-1963 (Box 11, Folder 346-353)
  - Hulcher, Wendell E., 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 354)
  - Hum-Hur (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Hut-Hy (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Hutchinson, W.H. (*), 1968-1978 (Box 11, Folder 358)
  - 'H' unidentified (Box 11, Folder 359)
  - I-Im (Box 11, Folder 360)
  - Illinois, University of, Press (*), 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 361-363)
  - Ing-Ins (Box 11, Folder 364)
  - Institute of International Education (*), 1951-1971 (Box 11, Folder 365-368)
  - Int (Box 11, Folder 369)
  - Io-Is (Box 11, Folder 370)
  - Iv (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - Jack (Box 12, Folder 372)
  - Jackson, Gardner (*), 1947-1963 (Box 12, Folder 373)
  - Jacksonville (Florida), City of, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 374)
  - Jaco-Jam (Box 12, Folder 375)
  - Jan-Jav (Box 12, Folder 376)
  - Je (Box 12, Folder 377)
  - Johnson, B-N (Box 12, Folder 378)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (*), 1956-1968 (Box 12, Folder 379)
  - Johnson, R-W (Box 12, Folder 380)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1966, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 381)
  - Johnst-Jor (Box 12, Folder 382)
  - Jones, Joseph M., 1946-1951 (Box 12, Folder 383)
  - Jos-Ju (Box 12, Folder 384)
  - 'J' unidentified (Box 12, Folder 385)
  - Kah-Kan (Box 12, Folder 386)
  - Kap-Kas (Box 12, Folder 387)
  - Kat-Kay (Box 12, Folder 388)
  - Katsuki, Hiroshi (*), 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 389)
  - Kea-Kell (Box 12, Folder 390)
  - Kels-Kene (Box 12, Folder 391)
  - Keni-Kenn (Box 12, Folder 392)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 393)
    See also: box 12, folder 394-397 See also: box 21, folder 726
  - Kennedy Writers Bureau (*), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 394-397)
  - Kent-Kerr (Box 12, Folder 398)
  - Kenyon College (*), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 399)
  - Kes-Key (Box 12, Folder 400)
  - Kie-Kim (Box 12, Folder 401)
  - Kilpatrick, Carroll (*), 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 402)
  - King (Box 12, Folder 403)
  - Kings-Kirk (Box 12, Folder 404)
  - Kirkp-Kj (Box 12, Folder 405)
  - Kl (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Kna-Knop (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Kno - Kog (Box 12, Folder 408)
  - Knowles, Horace (*), 1968-1978 (Box 12, Folder 409-410)
  - Koh-Koy (Box 13, Folder 411)
  - Kolderie, Ted (*), 1968-1975 (Box 13, Folder 412)
  - Kouwenhoven, John (*), 1944-1965 (Box 13, Folder 413)
  - Kra-Krish (Box 13, Folder 414)
  - Krist-Kro (Box 13, Folder 415)
  - Kru-Ky (Box 13, Folder 416)
  - 'K' unidentified (Box 13, Folder 417)
  - Laa-Lac (Box 13, Folder 418)
  - Lad-Lama (Box 13, Folder 419)
  - Lamb-Land (Box 13, Folder 420)
  - Lane-Larr (Box 13, Folder 421)
  - Lapham, Lewis H. (*), 1974, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 422-423)
  - Lars-Lass (Box 13, Folder 424)
  - Lau-Laz (Box 13, Folder 425)
  - Laune, Irene (Mrs. Paul) (*), 1968-1978 (Box 13, Folder 426-427)
  - Lea-Lee (Box 13, Folder 428)
  - Lee, Richard C., 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 429)
  - Leet-Lef (Box 13, Folder 430)
  - Leh-Lep (Box 13, Folder 431)
  - Lehman, Herbert H.
    See: box 1, folder 16
  - Leighton, George R. (*), 1934-1936 (Box 13, Folder 432)
  - Ler-Levin (Box 13, Folder 433)
  - Levine-Lewin (Box 13, Folder 434)
  - Lewis (Box 13, Folder 435)
  - Lewis, David (*), 1935-1948, 1976, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 436)
  - Lib-Lie (Box 13, Folder 437)
  - Lig-Linc (Box 13, Folder 438)
  - Lind-Lindq (Box 13, Folder 439)
  - Linds-Lip (Box 13, Folder 440)
  - List-Little (Box 13, Folder 441)
  - Littled-Liv (Box 13, Folder 442)
  - Ll (Box 13, Folder 443)
  - Loc-Loe (Box 13, Folder 444)
  - Lof-Lom (Box 13, Folder 445)
  - Lomax, Almena (*), 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 446)
  - Lon-Lor (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - Los-Lou (Box 13, Folder 448)
  - Lov-Lowenf (Box 13, Folder 449)
  - Lowent-Lub (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - Luce, Henry R.
    See: box 22, folder 775
  - Lud-Lund (Box 14, Folder 451)
  - Lunt-Ly (Box 14, Folder 452)
  - Lynes, Russell (*), 1944, 1968-1975, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 453-454)
  - 'L' unidentified (Box 14, Folder 455)
  - Mab-MacCa (Box 14, Folder 456)
  - MacCl-MacCo (Box 14, Folder 457)
  - MacCr-MacD (Box 14, Folder 458)
  - McCune, Shannon (*), 1944-1970, undated (Box 14, Folder 459-462)
  - MacDuffie, Marshall (*), 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 463-464)
  - McEuen, Ronald (*), 1944-1955 (Box 14, Folder 465)
  - MacF-MacGo (Box 14, Folder 466)
  - MacGr-Macka (Box 14, Folder 467)
  - Machemer, Corona (*), 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 468-470)
  - Mackea-Mackee (Box 14, Folder 471)
  - Macken-Macki (Box 14, Folder 472)
  - MacL-MacMa (Box 14, Folder 473)
  - MacLeish, Archibald (*), 1971-1978 (Box 14, Folder 474-475)
  - MacMahon, Arthur W., 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 476)
  - MacMi-MacP (Box 14, Folder 477)
  - MacMullen, Edie (Mrs. Ramsey) (*), 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 478)
  - MacQ-Macy (Box 14, Folder 479)
  - Mad (Box 14, Folder 480)
  - Mag-Maha (Box 14, Folder 481)
  - Mahl-Male (Box 14, Folder 482)
  - Malk-Mann (Box 14, Folder 483)
  - Manr-Marc (Box 14, Folder 484)
  - Mari-Mark (Box 15, Folder 485)
  - Markle (John and Mary R.) Foundation (*), 1960-1967 (Box 15, Folder 486-487)
  - Marq-Mart (Box 15, Folder 488)
  - Martin, John Bartlow (*), 1947, 1965-1978 (Box 15, Folder 489)
  - Masc-Maso (Box 15, Folder 490)
  - Mass-Matc (Box 15, Folder 491)
  - Massachusetts, University of (*), 1956, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 492)
    See also: box 14, folder 459-462
  - Math-Matt (Box 15, Folder 493)
  - Mau-Mayer, M (Box 15, Folder 494)
  - Maverick, Maury, Jr. (*), 1952-1953, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 495-496)
  - Mayer, Milton (*), 1966-1975 (Box 15, Folder 497)
  - Mayer, O-Mayr (Box 15, Folder 498)
  - Mea-Mend (Box 15, Folder 499)
  - Menk-Merce (Box 15, Folder 500)
  - Merch-Met (Box 15, Folder 501)
  - Mey (Box 15, Folder 502)
  - Mic-Mie (Box 15, Folder 503)
  - Mile-Miller, M (Box 15, Folder 504)
  - Miller, Helen Hill (*), 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 505)
  - Miller, P-W (Box 15, Folder 506)
  - Mills-Min (Box 15, Folder 507)
  - Mit-Mom (Box 15, Folder 508)
  - Mitford, Nancy
    See: box 19, folder 658
  - Moberg, Verne, 1962-1972 (Box 15, Folder 509)
  - Mon-Moon (Box 15, Folder 510)
  - Montgomery, Robert H. (*), 1937-1947 (Box 15, Folder 511)
  - Moor (Box 15, Folder 512)
  - More-Morri (Box 15, Folder 513)
  - Morris, Willie (*), 1962-1970, undated (Box 15, Folder 514)
  - Morro-Mors (Box 15, Folder 515)
  - Mort-Mosh (Box 15, Folder 516)
  - Mosl-Moyer (Box 15, Folder 517)
  - Moyers-Mull (Box 15, Folder 518)
  - Mulv-MY (Box 15, Folder 519)
  - Muskie, Edmund S., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 520)
  - 'M' unidentified (Box 15, Folder 521)
  - Naf-Nai (Box 16, Folder 522)
  - Nas-Nation (Box 16, Folder 523)
  - National A (Box 16, Folder 524)
  - National Book Committee, Inc., 1961-1968 (Box 16, Folder 525)
  - National Broadcasting Company, Inc., 1952-1968 (Box 16, Folder 526)
  - National C (Box 16, Folder 527)
  - National E (Box 16, Folder 528)
  - National Educational Television (*), 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 529-530)
    See also: box 5, folder 164 See also: box 7, folder 217 See also: box 18, folder 625-626
  - National F-W (Box 16, Folder 531)
  - National Municipal League (*), 1969-1977 (Box 16, Folder 532)
  - Naushon Trust (*), 1964-1969 (Box 16, Folder 533-534)
    See also: box 8, folder 250-251
  - Nay-Nel (Box 16, Folder 535)
  - Neo-Nes (Box 16, Folder 536)
  - Net-Nev (Box 16, Folder 537)
  - Neuberger, Richard L. (*), 1944-1954 (Box 16, Folder 538-539)
  - Neustadt, Richard E. (*), 1965 (Box 16, Folder 540)
  - New A-S (Box 16, Folder 541)
  - New Y (Box 16, Folder 542)
  - Newb-Newm (Box 16, Folder 543)
  - Newlands, Margot R. (*), 1944-1978, undated (Box 16, Folder 544-546)
  - News-Newt (Box 16, Folder 547)
  - Nic-Nieb (Box 16, Folder 548)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold (*), 1951, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 549)
  - Nied-Niem (Box 16, Folder 550)
  - Nid-Nob (Box 16, Folder 551)
  - Nisewaner, T. Andrew (*), 1935-1953, 1963-1978 (Box 16, Folder 552-553)
  - Nod-Norm (Box 16, Folder 554)
  - Norr-North (Box 16, Folder 555)
  - Norto-Not (Box 16, Folder 556)
  - Nov-Ny (Box 16, Folder 557)
  - 'N' unidentified (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - Oa-Ob (Box 17, Folder 559)
  - Oakes, George W. (*), 1947-1954 (Box 17, Folder 560)